# ADITI RANA

## PRODUCT MANAGER

### CONTACT

+91 9878220644 aditirana147@gmail.com

## **SKILLS**

Branding
Copywriting
Communication
Content Marketing
Data Understanding
Leveraging Al-tools
Strategic thinking

## **EDUCATION**

S.D. College, Panjab University **Bachelor of Arts** 

#### **PROFILE**

With 4.5 years of experience in Marketing – copywriting, branding and strategy; I've curated content for big names like PrepLadder, TVF, and Unacademy.

I excel in creating sky bus ads, managing social media, creating campaigns with high conversion rates and product branding that drives revenue!

## **EXPERIENCE**

Product Manager

## Bajaj Finserv Health, Pune | March 2023 – Present

- Identified flaws in the existing journey, led UX initiatives to reduce the drop-off rates by 58%
- Spearheaded brand integration, completing it in record-time, accelerating time-to-market & boosting user engagement.

Manager, Content Marketing

# Bajaj Finserv Health, Pune | November 2022 – April 2023

- Created an in-house AI Content tool, increasing operational efficiency by 60%.
- Executed branding & content for an on-site event called as Health Day Out within 24-hours
- Developed & executed content strategy increasing site traffic by 30% via SEO-optimized blog posts while mentoring freshers
- Created UX/UI content for mobile apps, improved retention rates by 25% & decreased user drop off!
- Managed social media campaigns, resulting in a 57% rise in follower engagement.
- Streamlined in-house business comms by strategically creating templates to improve stakeholder engagement, & creating better brand recall

Junior Content Writer

# Brand Th3ory, Mohali | October 2020 – September 2022

- Social media strategies for top brands like Unacademy,
   Snapchat, & TVF, increasing engagement by 35%.
- High-impact ad campaigns published in leading Indian newspapers, resulting in significant increase in product sales.
- Led and handled end-to-end marketing for more accounts than 3 other writers combined, without missing deadlines.